moveinsync.com 2015-04-16

# MoveInSync

MoveInSync Technology Solutions Private Limited (MIS) is committed to highest standards of customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about MIS information gathering and dissemination practices.

Please note that MIS privacy policy is subject to change at any time with or without prior notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, MIS requests you to review this policy periodically.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

MIS may collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number etc.) from you when you set up an account with [www.moveinsync.com](http://www.moveinsync.com/).

While you can browse some sections of MIS site without being a registered member, certain activities may require registration. MIS does use your contact information to contact you for business reasons. 

**Use of Demographic and Profile Data**

MIS uses personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent MIS uses your personal information to provide services to you, MIS shall provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. MIS uses your personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, help promote a safe service, collect fees owed, measure consumer interest in MIS products and services, inform you products, services, updates, customize your experience, detect and protect you against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce MIS terms and conditions and as otherwise may be described to you. In MIS efforts to continually improve MIS product and service offerings, MIS collects and analyzes demographic and profile data about MIS users’ activity on MIS website. MIS identifies and uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with MIS server, and to administer MIS website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. MIS will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information. MIS will not share your profile information with any other organization to let them use it for marketing purposes.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

MIS may share personal information with other corporate entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts, correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of MIS services, and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. 

MIS may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. MIS may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce MIS Terms or Privacy Policy, respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of MIS users or the general public. [www.moveinsync.com](http://www.moveinsync.com/) and its affiliates will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should MIS (or MIS assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

MIS site may link to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. [www.moveinsync.com](http://www.moveinsync.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.
